http://www.blackcatmusic.co.uk/privacy-policy

Telephone: 01892 619719 | Freephone: 0800 0727799 | Email: sales@blackcatmusic.co.uk
Select Website
My cart:
Shop By Department
Music Stands & AccessoriesMusic StandsMusic Stand LightsMusic Stand Storage BagsMusic Stand Storage CartsMusic FoldersMusic Chairs & AccessoriesMusic ChairsMusic StoolsMusic Chair Storage CartsMusic Chair AccessoriesInstrument & Music StorageMusical Instrument StorageSheet Music StorageConductors EquipmentConductors StandsConductors PodiumsConductors ChairsPiano AccessoriesStaging & RisersStagingChoral RisersTheatre ProductsWhiteboards & WorkstationsMusic WhiteboardsMusic WorkstationsAcoustic Products and SoundproofingModular Practice RoomsAcoustic ShellsClearance Items
All Categories
Music Stands & AccessoriesMusic StandsMusic Stand LightsMusic Stand Storage BagsMusic Stand Storage CartsMusic FoldersMusic Chairs & AccessoriesMusic ChairsMusic StoolsMusic Chair Storage CartsMusic Chair AccessoriesInstrument & Music StorageMusical Instrument StorageSheet Music StorageConductors EquipmentConductors StandsConductors PodiumsConductors ChairsPiano AccessoriesStaging & RisersStagingChoral RisersTheatre ProductsWhiteboards & WorkstationsMusic WhiteboardsMusic WorkstationsAcoustic Products and SoundproofingModular Practice RoomsAcoustic ShellsClearance Items
Privacy Policy
Home
Privacy Policy - Black Cat Music Ltd
Document Version & History
Version 0.1 – Dated 09.05.2018 until superseded.
We have versioned and dated our policies so as our customers (Data Subjects) have full Transparency over the Privacy, Data Protection & Processing terms in which they will have engaged with at the time of their interaction. Policies are not static and need to be updated as and when legal and business needs arise. However, this does not mean that the obligations and rights confided in those historical policies should be forgotten for the Data Subject and Black Cat Music Ltd as the Data Controller
Purpose
This document sets out the way Black Cat Music Ltd (Data Controller) and any 3rd parties we engage with (Data Processors) will collect, process and handle your Personal Data and your rights in that relationship as Data Subjects.
Basis in Law
This Policy is written to align with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) Legislation, enacted in April 2016 for EU Member states, and to be enforced as of 25th May 2018. The UK will replace / repeal the Data Protection Act (DPA) and replace it with the GDPR version.
Whilst the UK is currently under the regulation of the DPA, this policy goes much further than is currently required under the obligations of the DPA.
Principles
We will adhere to the following principles of the GDPR with respect to this Policy and our behaviours in which we are Guardians, not owners, of your personal data. These are:
Lawfulness, Fairness & Transparency
Purpose Limitation
Data minimisation & Proportionality
Data Quality & Accuracy
Storage Limitation
Integrity & Confidentiality
Accountability
Direct / Active Personal Data Collection
Information Provision by you directly, by being aware of the act of doing so, that contains Personal Data. We will, where possible BEFORE we collect your data, always notify you of:
the Data Protection Officer (DPO) of Black Cat Music Ltd and ICO registration.
the Purpose of Data Collection and Processing.
the Legal Basis of Data Collection and Processing.
the intention to transfer (or not) of Personal Data to a 3rd party or organisation.
the intention to transfer (or not) of Personal Data to a 3rd country and the legal basis of that.
the duration / time we will store your information.
your rights as a Data Subject in terms of your personal data:
Right of Access Right to Object Right to Portability
Right of Restriction
Right to Erasure
Right to be Forgotten
Passive / Indirect Personal Data Collection
Information Provision by you, indirectly collected by not necessarily being aware of the act of doing so, that contains your Personal Data.
We will, where possible before we collect your data or within 1 month, always notify you of:
the Source of the Personal Data collected.
the Data Protection Officer (DPO) of Black Cat Music Ltd and ICO registration.
the Purpose of Data Collection and Processing.
the Legal Basis of Data Collection and Processing.
the intention to transfer (or not) of Personal Data to a 3rd party or organisation.
the intention to transfer (or not) of Personal Data to a 3rd country and the legal basis of that.
the duration / time we will store your information.
your rights as a Data Subject in terms of:
Right of Access
Right to Object
Right to Portability
Right of Restriction
Right to Erasure
Right to be Forgotten
3rd Party Indirectly Acquired Personal Data Collection
Information Provision to us about you indirectly collected whereby you are not aware of the act of doing so, that contains your Personal Data.
We will, as soon as possible and within 1 month, always notify you of:
the Source of the Personal Data collected.
the Data Protection Officer (DPO) of Black Cat Music Ltd and ICO registration.
the Purpose of Data Collection and Processing.
the Legal Basis of Data Collection and Processing.
the intention to transfer (or not) of Personal Data to a 3rd party or organisation.
the intention to transfer (or not) of Personal Data to a 3rd country and the legal basis of that.
the duration / time we will store your information.
your rights as a Data Subject in terms of:
Right of Access
Right to Object
Right to Portability
Right of Restriction
Right to Erasure
Right to be Forgotten
Terms
Term
Definition
Black Cat Music Ltd
‘us’ ‘the company’ ‘Data Controller’
3rd Party
‘Data Processor’ / ‘Contracted Entity’ / ‘Indirect Source’
Privacy Policy
This document and its contents
Personal Data
Any information relating to and identified or identifiable natural person
Data Collection
Method of Personal Data acquired by the Data Controller about the Data Subject.
Data Processing
Method by which Personal Data may be manipulated.
Data Subject
The natural person for which personal data applies to and is processed
Data Controller
The legal entity or person that makes decisions on collecting and processing personal data. ‘Black Cat Music Ltd’
Data Processor
The legal entity or person that processes personal data on behalf of the data controller. ‘3rd Party’ ‘Contracted Entity’
3rd Party Indirectly Acquired Personal Data Collection
Information Provision to us about you indirectly collected whereby you are not aware of the act of doing so, that contains your Personal Data e.g bought in marketing details
Passive / Indirect Personal Data Collection
Information Provision by you indirectly collected by not necessarily being aware of the act of doing so, that contains your Personal Data e.g Cookies via our website
Direct / Active Personal Data Collection
Information Provision by you directly by being aware of the act of doing so, that contains your Personal Data e.g Contact Us website form
